本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 修正调整
欢迎爱好者加入我们 www.YYeTs.com
字幕来源:   网络收集
字幕修正 & 补翻:   LCHAOS       后期 & 双语合成:   LCHAOS
女生们先生们  飞机马上就要在莫斯科着陆了
Ladies and gentlemen, we have begun our descent into Moscow.
请关闭所有便携式电子设备
Please turn off all portable electronic devices.
谢谢合作
Thank you.
先生  你能把那个关掉吗
Sir, could you please turn that off?
它会干扰到飞机的导航系统
It can interfere with the plane's navigation system.
你真的相信吗
Do you really believe that?
因为人们在上机前
Because people have been talking
已经谈论过乘务员的话是否可信
outside the flight attendant social circle of trust,
结果是  没人相信她们
and word is that nobody really believes that.
原谅我的朋友  他小时候脑袋给门夹了
Excuse my friend. He was dropped on his head as a child.
真的  如果真的那么危险的话
No. If these were really that bad,
他们根本就不会让你带这些东西上来  直接否决
they wouldn't let you bring them on the plane, flat out.
如果你同意我的话  不用举手赞同
If you agree with me, don't unfold your arms.
看到了吗?
See?
哥们  你就非得在这时候玩多拉大冒险吗?
Dude, do you really need an extra minute of playing Dora the Explorer?
水晶王国就快通关了
She was about to save the Crystal Kingdom.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
刚才只是一次电气短路
We just experienced an electrical short.
在你的右边  平流层上部
To your right, you will see heavy electrical activity
你会看到强烈的雷电活动
in the upper stratosphere.
不用过于担心的
Nothing of major concern.
我讨厌坐飞机
I hate flying.
由于雷电风暴  所有出航的航班都取消了
Due to electrical storms, all outbound flights are canceled.
你上一次穿这衣服是什么时候
When was the last time you wore that?
不清楚  毕业典礼吧?
I don't know. Graduation?
你根本就没参加毕业典礼
You didn't go to graduation.
出于相互支持  那天我还是有穿
But I still dressed up out of solidarity.
行了  给我支油性笔
All right, give me a Sharpie.
总有一天  我不会带它在身上的
One of these days, I'm not going to have a Sharpie in my bag.
-又挖苦我? -没错
-Another poignant metaphor for me? -Yes.
这是款为环球旅行的游客设计的社交网络
It's an exclusive social network for globetrotting travelers.
基于GPS导航系统  可以让年轻人
It's a GPS-based navigation system that allows young people
随时随地都能找到最火爆的酒吧和夜店
to find the hottest bars and clubs in cities around the world.
我们来莫斯科的扩展计划是
Our expansion plans for Moscow...
Sean?
你神游去了?
Jump in whenever.
这次来莫斯科的扩展计划包括烂醉  滥交
Our expansion plans for Moscow include getting drunk, laid
最后免费参观俄国监狱  一切只需轻点鼠标
and ending up in a Russian prison, all at the click of a button.
是我的问题  还是这些斯拉夫语看起来像克林贡语
Is it just me, or does Cyrillic look like Klingon?
拜托  你认真点
Dude, get serious for a second.
我刚看到"明星酒吧"了
Come on, man. I found that freaky Zvezda joint
我们这次肯定能凯旋而归
we're going to hit up for our victory lap.
"超模们为软件设计师神魂颠倒"
"Supermodels desperately seeking software designers."
这主意不错
That's a good idea.
等俄国佬想分一杯羹时
And when the Russians go for this,
我们一夜间  就成千万级的公司了
we're a $10-million company overnight.
莫斯科现在有56个游客登录
Fifty-six travelers currently logged into Moscow.
是个美国人
Ooh, an American.
我飞了半个地球  可不是来看美国人的
I didn't fly halfway around the world to see Americans.
领她去"苹果蜂"(美国连锁餐厅)
Tell her to go to Applebee's.
明星酒吧? 明星酒吧
Zvezda? Zvezda.
-Ben? -怎么了
-Ben? -Yeah?
我有让你失望过吗?
Have I ever let you down?
有
Yeah.
我们会让Skyler做产品介绍
We'll let Skyler make the introductions.
在这儿等我们
Wait for us.
准备好了吗
You ready?
团队合作  所向披靡
Teamwork makes the dream work.
真是太扯了
That's ridiculous.
伙计们  你们来这儿干嘛?
Whoa, guys. What are you doing here?
没收到我发的邮件吗
Didn't you get my e-mail?
我们不需要你们了
We won't be needing you.
等等  我兄弟为了这个项目  花了差不多1万2
Hang on. My boy just spent, like, 12 grand to develop this.
还得加上机票钱
Plus, flights.
没错  怎么回事  这明明就是我的创意
Yeah, what the hell is going on here? Looks exactly like my idea.
对  我知道  几乎完美了  谢谢你
Yeah, I know. It's very good. It's almost perfect, thank you.
下次记得要签保密协议
Next time, you send an NDA.
你一定是说"非混蛋协议"吧
You must mean the Non-Douchebag Agreement.
叫保安
Call security.
Skyler  你为什么这么做
Whoa, whoa. Skyler, why are you doing this?
这叫生意
It's business.
这是犯罪
It's criminal.
欢迎来到莫斯科
Welcome to Moscow.
保安会带你们出去的
Security will help see you out.
真是太扯了
This is such bullshit.
-看这儿  -我知道太美了
-Look at this place. -I know, right?
美极了
It's amazing.
美极了  可我们迷路了
Amazing, but are we lost?
不  地图上显示  离我们只有两条街远了
No. This map says we're only two blocks away.
好的  等下
All right. Hold up, hold up.
-一起说"莫斯科" -莫斯科
-Everyone say, "Moscow." -Moscow.
-我们是怎么找到这儿的  -通过这个家伙的博客
-So how did we find this place? -This guy's blog.
-帅不帅  -还行
-Cute? -Yeah,
我是说左边那个
I mean, if he's the one on the left.
Nat  他朋友居然穿毛毯衣打牛仔领带
Nat, his friend is wearing a Snuggie with a bolo tie.
我知道你最爱了  别想骗我
I know you're into that, don't lie.
对  如果我去这个邋遢家伙的地下室
Yeah, if I end up some human lampshade in this guy's creepy basement...
放心  我一定给你找个不邋遢的
Relax. I'm giving you a no-lampshade guarantee.
走吧?
Shall we?
去喝点东西
We shall have a drink.
我们一定要到那上面  好吗
I'm like, "We have to go up there, right?"
?I like the Gucci, Gucci I like the dollar bill?
?I love your pocket rocket We live to shock it, shock it?
?I like the way you smile I might just bite your lip?
?I see you talking, talking Your hands are talking, talking?
?I like that?
?I like your dirty mind Mine's on it all the time?
?Oh, let me shake it, shake it, Oh, Polaroid it, shake it?
?I'm a graffiti girl?
算了  往好处想  这根本没关系
Screw it. Big picture, this doesn't mean shit.
关系大了
It does mean shit.
我们的未来  全在这上面了
Our future is exactly shit right now.
我们去告这些人
Okay. We'll sue those guys.
找一个牛逼的  懂俄罗斯法律的国际律师
Get a huge international Matlock-ass lawyer who knows Russian law.
什么俄罗斯法律?
What Russian law?
别灰心好吗  我们会有办法的
Just don't sweat it, all right? We'll figure something out.
-你怎么会这样子? -什么样
-How can you be like that? -Like what?
总是盲目的乐观
Like delusionally optimistic all the time.
我只是有过  比你现在更糟糕的过去
I'm just more used to screwing up than you are.
我想对你发火
I try and get mad at you.
孩子  看灯柱那边
Son, peep the kiosk.
妞全在灯柱旁边
Full on kiosk.
那个肯嫁给我的
Kiosk her to marry me.
不是吧?
Seriously?
那个瑞典傻逼
That Swedish prick.
伙计们  你在这儿
Guys, you're here.
真是厉害  那个研究真棒
It's impressive. That's good research.
你们不会这么天真吧
Look. You can't be so naive, okay?
我是说  你们来到这儿
I mean, you come out here,
这儿其他人全是饿狼  而你们却像两只小羊羔
everybody out here is like hungry wolves, and you act like two little lambs?
难怪你们会被吃掉
Of course you're going to get eaten.
你可以把自己想象成一匹狼  这样才能在夜里睡得着
You may like to think of yourself as a wolf so you can sleep at night,
可事实是  你是个彻头彻尾的贼
but the truth is, you're just a straight-up thief.
你得明白  这是生意
You have to understand, this is just business.
有些人做的来
Some people can take it.
有些人就不行
Some people can't.
衬衫不错
It's a nice shirt.
谢谢  你妈昨天忘在我房间里的
Oh, thanks. Your mom left it in my room.
没有哪个社会不存在酒精和信仰
No human society exists without booze or religion.
所以我信仰喝酒
That's why I drink religiously.
哥们  是那个美国人
Dude, the American.
是吗
Oh, really?
"困在莫斯科请求帮助"
"Stuck in Moscow. Please help."
苹果峰  算了
Applebee's, never mind.
我们该去帮忙
We should help.
不是! 不是!
Nyet! Nyet!
-同性恋  -对
-Lesbian. -Yeah.
疱疹
Herpes.
非常感谢
Muchas gracias.
谢谢  先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.
做的挺好  谢谢你
Good job. Thank you.
那个穿毛毯衣的  六点钟方向  我跟你说了  他朋友好帅
Snuggie, six o' clock. I told you his friend is hot.
真有你的
You and your valedictorians.
"困在莫斯科请求帮助"
"Stuck in Moscow. Please help"?
环球旅行者网站
Theglobetrot. Com.
现已正式退休了
Now officially retired.
怎么了? 你们该不会是百万富翁什么的吧?
What happened? Are you guys some kind of millionaires or something?
不是  想想亿万富翁
No, no. Try billionaire.
或是好朋友和满嘴跑火车的搭档
Uh... Or just the loyal friend of a full-of-shit wingman?
-我是Ben  -我是满嘴跑火车搭档
-I'm Ben. -Full-of-shit wingman.
我是Anne  她是Natalie
Anne. This is Natalie.
谢谢你们的提醒  完全符合我们想要的
Well, thanks for the tip. It's definitely living up to expectations.
其实是Sean的创意
Sean is actually the man who finds this stuff.
那你是做什么的?
And what do you do?
剩下的一切
Everything else.
你什么时候开始起身离开莫斯科? 妈
能给我来一杯啤酒吗
Can I get a lager? A beer?
有人会讲俄语吗
Does anyone speak Russian?
只在《洛奇4》里学过几句
Only what he learned in Rocky IV.
总之  我本在去尼泊尔的路上  正在拍照
So, anyway, I'm on my way to Nepal. Shooting photos.
我想把他们放进我的画廊
I'm trying to get them into this gallery.
你会的
You will get in.
Nat是我最忠实的助手和闺蜜
Nat, here, is my faithful assistant and my best girl.
这个夏天  我本已有别的打算了  但后来都泡汤了
Well, I did have other plans this summer, but they fell through,
于是我辞职了  给我妈留了个纸条  就跑到这了
so I quit my job and I left my mom a note. And here I am.
你为什么这么做啊
Why would you do that?
一个混蛋男人
A dumbass boy.
好的  能不能不谈这些
Okay, can we not talk about that?
对不起
Sorry.
你究竟是做什么的?
So, what do you actually do?
对  做哪行的
Yeah, what do you do?
他喜欢到处撞运气
He likes basking in the possibility.
是吗
Right?
还是从不用承诺什么
Or just never having to commit to anything.
你有点坏
You're kind of a dick.
拍照时间
Photo time.
没笨蛋相  不假正经  都聚过来
No dumbass faces, no peace signs. Come on, now.
-好的  -好的
-Okay, okay. -All right.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
这么回事?
What?
抱歉  伙计们  我的错
Sorry, guys, my bad.
你又干了什么  Sean?
What did you do now, Sean?
俄罗斯啊
Russia.
发生什么了
What's happening?
那是什么啊
What is that?
北极光吧
Northern Lights, maybe?
我还从没见过呢
I've never seen this before.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
我手机没电了
My phone is dead.
整个街道一片黑暗
The whole block is dark.
-天呐  -真漂亮
-My God. -They're beautiful.
这可不正常
This isn't normal, bud.
天呐
Holy shit.
Nat
Nat.
看那个
Look at that.
Sean  你看见了吗
Sean, you see that?
他要干吗
What's he doing?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
跑
Run!
-快跑  -快跑  快跑  快跑
-Go! -Run! Run! Run! Run!
Natalie  快跑
Natalie! Come on!
待在一块
Stay together!
锁上
Lock it!
快跑
Run!
快
Move.
快啊  快啊
Come on! Come on!
老天啊
Oh, my God.
-我操  -天呐
-Fuck. -Oh, my God.
快啊  快跑
Come on! Come on! Come on!
-这边  -快  快
-This way. -Go, go, go, go!
快跑
Go!
天呐  快
Holy shit! Come on!
这边  快走
This way. Come on!
快啊  快啊
Come on, come on.
Ben  快来啊
Ben! Let's go!
快进去  快
Get in there. Go, go, go.
-快啊  这边  -Annie
-Come on. This way. -Annie!
Sean!
快
Come on.
-天啊  -操
-Oh, my God. -Shit.
Ben?
Natalie! Natalie!
-那是什么啊  -我不知道
-What the hell was that? -I don't know. I don't know.
-我们该怎么办  -他死了
-What are we going to do? -He's dead.
好了  好了
It's okay. It's okay.
该死
Oh, shit.
不  不  不要  不要
No! No! No! No!
不要开门
Don't open the door!
天呐
Oh, God.
他们要干嘛? 那些东西见谁杀谁
What do they want? They're killing everyone.
把人都撕裂了
They're shredding people.
-你看见了吗  -不
-Did you see that? -No!
安静  安静  都安静
Quiet, quiet, quiet! Holy shit!
那是什么啊? 哪来的
What is it? Where did it come from?
Annie  怎么回事
Annie, what's going on?
天呐
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
怎么...
What the...
不  不
No, no.
上面不安全  我看到它们了
It isn't safe up there. I saw it.
这些是什么东西啊
What the hell are those things?
他们隐形  我们看不到
It's like they're invisible. We can't see them.
发生什么了
What's happening?
无处可逃  它们到处都是
There's nowhere to go, they're everywhere.
大家都安静
Everybody, be quiet.
你觉得就你自己困在这儿了吗
Do you really think that you're the only person down here?
来啊  来啊
Come on! Oh, come on!
我厌倦你的废话了  我受够...
I'm sick and tired of your bullshit, man! I'm sick and tired...
就这个了
This is it.
祝你好胃口
Bon appétit.
对  还没吃够吗
Yeah, like, the thousandth time is a charm?
离上次听到声音  过去多久了
How long since we've heard them?
27个小时  或多或少一个小时
I said 27 hours. Give or take an hour.
除非你想在这儿  尿在铁罐子里一辈子
Unless you want to stay down here pissing in tin cans forever...
去他妈的
Screw that.
该走了
It's time to go.
我们去美国大使馆
We're going to head to the U.S. Embassy.
快来
Come on.
小心
Careful, now.
Ben  看这个
Ben. Look at this.
他们杀了所有人
They killed everyone.
简直是屠杀
It was a massacre.
我们该去瑞典大使馆
We should go to the Swedish Embassy, it's closer. We should really go...
Annie
Annie.
更近些  我们还是去找找水源  食物  补给
See if they have any water, food, supplies.
这儿  带上这些水
Here, take these waters.
找个包
Grab that bag.
能拿多少拿多少
Just take what you can.
拿上这个  走
Take this. Go.
天呐
Holy shit.
看这儿
Look at this place.
天呐
Oh, my God.
你觉得他们走了吗? 彻底的离开了吗?
You think they're gone? Like "gone" gone?
全是灰烬
All the ash.
整座城市全是这样吗?
Is it going to be like this all over the city?
肯定不只我们这些幸存者
We can't be the only ones.
你知道我们要去哪吗
Do you even know where we're going?
我可不想看着外卖地图就出发
I just wish we had a plan that didn't come from some takeout menu.
没人会发现我们躲在储藏室
Nobody's going to find us hiding in the storeroom.
留下  还是去大使馆  没人阻止你
Stay here, or find your embassy. Nobody's stopping you.
天呐
Jesus.
我们走
Let's go.
走了  Annie
Come on, Annie.
这是个大城市
It's a big city.
一定还有幸存者
There has to be more people out there.
慢点  慢点
Slow down. Slow down.
天呐
Oh, man.
你还好吗  你没事吧
-Shit. You okay? -You okay?
等等  伙计们
Just wait, guys.
-我没事  -等等
-Okay. I'm okay. -Wait.
好了  我们要继续走
Come on, we got to keep going.
-好了  继续走  -Natalie
-Come on. Let's keep going. -Natalie.
-走  -快
-Let's go. -Come on.
好了  加快速度
Come on, hurry up.
等等  等等  这边  快
Wait, wait, wait. This way, come on.
好了  一直走
Come on, down here.
是这条路吗
Is this the right way?
安静
Quiet.
等一下
Hang on a second.
等等  你听见了吗  这边
Wait, you hear that? Come on, this way.
那是什么
What's there?
等等
Wait.
快
Come on.
嘿  夫人
Hey! Hey, lady?
走开
Go away.
你会把幽灵引来的
You will bring ghosts with you.
走开
Go away.
诺维斯基大街?
Novinskiy Street?
城里所有人都死了
Everyone in the city is dead.
他们会杀了你的
They will kill you!
什么?
What?
那边
That way.
-Ben  继续走  -谢谢你
-Ben, keep moving. Let's go. -Thank you so much.
小心灯光
Beware of the lights.
-她说什么  -我们都会死了
-What did she say? -We're all going to die.
天呀
Oh, my God.
我们不知道他们在哪
We don't know where they are.
没事的
It's okay.
Ben  这条路对吗?
Ben. This way, right?
我们迷路了吗
Are we lost?
-该死的  我们迷路了  -没有
-God damn it, we're lost already! -We're not lost.
你知道在往哪走吗
Do you know where you're going?
兄弟  我们迷路了吗
Dude, are we lost?
没有  等我们过了桥
No, I think once we cross the bridge...
该死
Oh, shit.
这个团队没有希望  我们也不了解他们
This crew doesn't inspire confidence. We don't know anything about them.
我们还是走吧
It's the best we've got right now.
那边还有座桥
There's another bridge right over there.
重要的是  你和我在一起  好吗
What's important is that you and I stick together, okay?
他是对的
He's right.
伙计们  走了
Guys, come on.
往回走  快
It's back this way. Come on.
停下  停下
Stop, stop, stop.
-警车里会有地图  -对
-That cop car will have a better map. -Yeah, yeah.
你们在这儿等着  走
You guys wait over there. Let's go.
-好的  -好  走
-All right. -Okay, go.
那是什么?
What?
快  加速
Come on. Hurry up.
你看见了吗?
Did you see that?
给我  你花太多时间了
Give me that. You're taking too long.
不知道这些东西有没有视觉听觉
We don't know these things can see or hear.
只知道他们见人就杀
We know they kill.
-照明弹  -找到了
-Road flares. -Here we go.
全是俄语
It's all in Russian.
你还想什么啊
What did you expect?
从地标查街道
We'll count off blocks from landmarks.
不  等等  趴下  趴下
No! Wait. Get down. Get down.
到里面去
Get inside!
快  快
Go, go, go.
它在哪  能看见吗
Where did it go? Can you see it?
你看到什么了吗
Can you see anything?
该死
Shit!
-你在干嘛  -总要做些什么
-What are you doing? -Something.
走了吗
Is it gone?
我想是的
I think so.
天呐
Holy shit.
刚才好险
That was way too close.
Sean!
你们等我们了
Hey, you waited.
我们说好待在一起的
Yeah, yeah. That's the plan, right? Stick together?
很好  谢谢
Good. Thanks.
你看见那条狗了吗
Did you see that dog?
它杀了狗  它杀了狗
It killed the dog. It killed the dog.
等等  等等
Wait! Wait! Wait!
是风  别这么害怕好吗
It's the wind! Stop freaking out!
什么? 只有我很害怕吗?
What, me? I'm the only one freaking out here?
我也没想到我的周末会是这样子  好吗?
This wasn't how I thought my week would go either, all right?
我就不把害怕表现出来
I'm just trying to keep my freak-out on the inside!
从这边走
Let's cut through this way.
该死
Shit.
天呐
Oh, my God.
Skyler  走了
Skyler. Come on.
越快赶到大使馆  我们就越快回家
The faster we get to the embassy, the faster we get home.
家?
"Home"?
你觉得还有家?
You think there's "home"?
家里所有人都死了
Everybody back home is dead.
-你又不知道  -肯定是的
-You don't know that. -Of course they are.
所有的朋友  家人
All our friends, our families.
就算其他地方也是这样子
Say it's like this everywhere,
我们5个在莫斯科  还活着
the five of us, we're here, we're in Moscow, and we're alive.
对吗? 我们不是这地球上最幸运的5个人
Okay? I doubt we're the five luckiest people on the planet.
所以在世界各地  还有数不清的幸存者
Which makes for millions of survivors, in other cities, all over the world.
这又能怎么样呢  你不明白吗?
It doesn't even matter anymore. Don't you understand?
走错一步  就成灰了
I mean, we take one step outside and we're dust.
我们看不到这些东西
We can't even see these things.
刚才辆警车那儿
The way it lit up that cop car.
是电流把它驱走了
Electricity gives it away.
还有路灯  车灯
Street lights, headlights...
没错
You're right.
白天比晚上更危险
Daytime is more dangerous than night.
我们应该在天黑时行动
We should go outside when it's dark.
-用来做警告  -好主意
-Warning devices. -Good idea.
你没我想的那么蠢
Not as dumb as I thought.
大使馆应该只有一里远了
Looks like the embassy is about a mile away.
你这次能领对路吗
Are you going to get it right this time?
你能不能别这么混蛋了
Are you going to be less of an asshole?
我只是想选一个明智的建议
I just want us to make smart choices.
你这么称呼夜店发生的事情吗?
Is that what you call what happened at the club?
-做明智的选择  -Annie  不要
-Making a smart choice? -Annie, don't.
我想  内心里
I think we all want to be
我们都想做个勇敢的人
brave in our own minds.
可真相是  直到大事临头
But the truth is that you don't know who you are
你根本不知道自己是什么
until something happens.
接着便是本能反应
And then you just react.
我只是...
And I just...
那些画面在我脑海一遍遍重复
I see these two seconds just playing over and over and over again.
我们需要更好衣服
We need better clothes.
我去弄
I got it.
世界末日的  该穿什么衣服
What's the dress code for the end of the world?
夹克不打领带?
Jacket, no tie?
我也去
I'll come, too.
哥们
Hey, there.
抱歉啊  老兄  这件我得拿走
Sorry, buddy. I'm going to have to take this.
Sean!
等等  不要
Hey, wait. No.
-你疯了吗  -别动
-Are you crazy? -Don't move.
没事了  我们走
It's okay. Come on.
他们来了
They're inside.
-我们离这么近  它为什么没看到我们  -因为灯泡
-We were so close, why didn't it see us? -The glass.
-它没看到你吗  -没
-It didn't see you? -No.
它们应该可以察觉到生物电磁场之类的玩意
I bet they sense our bio-electromagnetic shit.
有些道理
That almost makes sense.
你怎么想到的?
How did you come up with that?
我也不知道  探索频道《鲨鱼周》上面说的
I don't know. Shark Week.
我打赌它们看的到我们的电脉冲
My money's on they see our electric pulses.
灯泡把它屏蔽了
And the glass blinded it.
就像电流绝缘体
It's an electrical insulator.
你愿意拿命去赌一把你的理论吗
You're willing to bet your life on that theory?
我们刚验证了
We just did.
我们走
Come on.
快  我们走
Come on, come on. Let's go.
这边
This way.
该死
Oh, shit.
你还想什么呢
What did you expect?
现在怎么办
What do we do now?
现在去哪
Where do we go?
快
Come on.
你要  你要干什么
What are you... What do you...
你打算拿它干什么
What are you going to do with that?
不知道  感觉挺好
I don't know. Feels good.
你知道怎么用吗?
You know how to use that thing?
知道
Yeah.
-停下  -Skyler
-Stop! -Skyler!
停下
Stop!
好了  我看够了  我们还是走吧
All right. I've seen enough. Let's just get the hell out of here.
往哪走?
And go where?
往上
Up.
该死的  Sean
God damn it, Sean!
天知道上面会有什么
We don't know what's up there.
照你这么说  我们该去哪
Or where we're going, for that matter.
听着  我们需要更好的视野
Listen, we need a better view.
一个能看到全局的地方  哪个方向安全
Somewhere where we can see what's going on. What direction's safe.
你们不要命了吗?
You guys want to get yourself killed?
Skyler  我们该待在一起
Skyler, we should stick together.
过来
Come on.
-Nat  我... -走吧
-Nat, I... -Come on.
我留在下面
I got it down here.
有人吗?
Hello?
布达佩斯1230  安特卫普621
Budapest, 1230. Antwerp, 621.
-这是时间吗  -可能吧
-Are these times? -Maybe.
伙计们  看这个
Guys, look at this.
电磁轰炸使得我们的硬件短路
"Their electromagnetic bombardment shorted our hardware.
不是导弹  不是战机
"No missiles. No jets."
不只是莫斯科
This wasn't just Moscow.
通信只保持了3分钟
"Communications stayed up for three minutes.
纽约  伦敦  巴黎  东京
"New York, London, Paris, Tokyo
均报道称  遭遇无形入侵者猛烈攻击
"all reported invisible invaders. Aggressive assault strategy."
Skyler说的对
Skyler was right.
无家可归了
There is no home.
-我好像不记得了  -天呐
-Not like we remember it. -Oh, God.
地下的硬件躲过了它们的首轮攻击
"Hardware from the underground survived their initial attack.
我们尽可能的挽救了一切
"We salvaged what we could,
希望能与安特卫普重新取得联系  布达佩斯
"hope to reconnect with Antwerp, Budapest."
这些不是时间
These aren't times.
而是幸存人数
These are numbers of survivors.
我们收到莫斯科同盟的紧急行动信息
"We found an Emergency Action Message from allies here in Moscow.
全球HF频率4-7-0-9...
"Global HF frequency 4-7-0-9..."
信息里说什么
What did the message say?
就这些
That's it.
看这个
Hey, check this out.
天呐
Oh, my God.
你说过  这些东西能看到电流  所以关掉好吗
You said those things see electricity, so turn it off.
-灯泡又没亮  -等等
-The bulbs aren't on. -Wait.
上面说什么
What's he saying?
-拜托  Sean  关掉好吗  -在重复
-Please, Sean, just turn it off, okay? -It's repeating.
一条信息
A message.
求你关掉!
Please turn it off!
这是如何工作的?
How is it working?
该死的  这些东西能看到的  关掉好吗?
God damn it, okay? Those things can see it, so turn it off!
Sean!
好了
Okay.
-天啊  -好了
-Jesus. -It's okay.
好了  我们去找视野
Come on. Let's find a view.
Ben? 这边  来  看
Ben? Over here, check this out.
天呐
Holy shit.
我们被包围了
We're surrounded.
死亡中心
Dead center.
他们在那儿干什么呢
What are they doing out there?
好像是在挖什么东西
It's like they're digging for something.
他们破坏一切电子设备
They mess with everything electrical.
他们一定遵守着某种规则  有某种目的
They got to obey some sort of rules, have some sort of purpose.
他们是有备而来的
They came here with a plan.
我们的呢
What's ours?
还有更多幸存者
There's more survivors.
一定有  我们得找到他们
We know they're out there, we just have to find them.
那是谁
Who is it?
Skyler
Skyler.
他在干什么
What the hell is he doing?
走  我们得阻止他
Come on. We gotta stop him.
等等  为什么啊
Wait, why?
他懂一些俄语
The guy understands some Russian.
他可以翻译信息
He can translate the message for us.
小心
Be careful.
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
不
Oh, no.
No.
不  不  不  不要
No, no, no, no, no!
Sean!
不
No.
必须要提醒他们
We have to warn them.
快
Now!
Skyler!
回来!
Get back here!
等等  我好像有看到什么东西
Wait, wait, I think I saw something.
该死  Skyler!
Oh, shit. Skyler!
操
Oh, shit!
Ben!
真该死
Oh, shit.
-小心  -他被困住了
-Look out! -He's trapped.
离开这儿
Get out of here!
快跑
Run!
Sean  赶快
Sean, come on.
快  右边
Come on. Right.
不!
No!
Skyler人呢?
Where's Skyler?
他死了! 他死了!
He's dead, he's dead. He's dead.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊...
Oh, my...
我不能这样
I can't do this.
-你能  你能的  -不  我做不到
-Yes, you can! Yes, you can! -No, I can't do this.
-你必须去做  -我们只是在争取时间
-You have to! -All we're doing is buying time.
快看
Look at this.
Skyler看见的  就是这个
That's got to be what Skyler saw.
有什么东西在里面
There's someone in there.
不是很远
It's not that far.
太阳要升起来了  不可能的
The sun is about to come up. No way.
我们可以的
We can make it.
Sean  你怎么了?
Sean, what is wrong with you?
看看SkyIer的下场  我们也会有同样的下场的
After what just happened to Skyler? That could happen to any one of us.
听我说  他还活着  就在我们中间
Listen to me! That person is surviving, right in the middle of all this.
不论是谁
Whoever it is,
他们肯定都会明白
odds are they're going to understand this message.
走吧
Let's go.
我是不会放弃的
I'm not giving up.
我都不放弃  你也要坚持下去
And if I'm not giving up, you're not giving up.
那我们还在等什么?
What are we waiting for?
是的
-We're almost there, right? -Yeah.
快  太阳快升起来了
Hurry, the sun's coming up.
快  穿过这儿
Come on. Through here.
你到底是谁?
Who the hell are you?
你想死么? 混蛋
Do you want to die, assholes?
我们看见灯光了
We saw the light.
下次记得敲门
Next time, knock.
你爸妈在吗?
Are your parents here?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事的
It's okay.
我挺得住
I'm tough.
来这边  跟我来
Come this way. Come with me.
你找到没?
Did you find one?
找到了
Yes.
很好
Ah, good.
Sergei?
快点  我们得把笼子关上
Quickly, we must close the cage!
欢迎光临  请随意
Welcome, make yourself at home.
你好年轻
You're young
年轻人就是很莽撞
and young people make rash decisions.
但这也就是你和Vika活下来的原因
It's why you and Vika are still alive.
我听不太懂俄语
We don't really understand much Russian.
Sean
Sean.
我把灯光打开吸引幸存者
I turned on the light to attract survivors.
女孩先来了  然后就是你们
First the girl, then you.
我叫Vika
I'm Vika.
那个是DJ Lance Rock
That's DJ Lance Rock.
这家伙是谁?
Who is this guy?
Sergei先生
Mr. Sergei.
我想他是个电工
I think he's an electrician.
也可能是个水管工
Or maybe a plumber.
好吧  这是什么?
Well, what is this?
Sergei先生称它为达拉第笼
Mr. Sergei calls it a Faraday cage.
铁棒连接外部电流
The steel bars ground external electrical currents.
笼子就可以工作了
The cage, it works.
也就是说  他们不会靠近这个?
You mean it keeps them away?
我们在里面  他们就不能察觉到
They can't smell us if we're inside.
这可是个鲨鱼笼  伙计
It's a shark cage, bro.
Sergei先生认为  他们是由波能构成的
Mr. Sergei thinks they're made up of wave energy.
是致命的波能
They are made up of lethal wave energy.
所以我们看不见他们
That's why they're invisible to us.
他说他们袭击莫斯科
He says they microwaved Moscow.
烧毁了一切
Burned everything out.
伙计们  有消息
Hey, guys, the message.
Vika  你来听听这个
Vika, you've got to listen to this.
它是在重复广播还是什么
It's repeating a broadcast or something.
Nikolai Ivanov长官
"Captain Nikolai lvanov
来自K152Nerpa
"from the K-1-5-2 Nerpa..."
我的天
Oh, my God.
俄罗斯海军
The Russian Navy.
有一艘核潜艇
A nuclear submarine
在莫斯科河
in the Moskva River.
他们明天早上六点出发
They leave tomorrow morning at 6:00.
屏蔽核电  是一个海底法拉第笼
Shielded nuclear power. An undersea Faraday cage.
很聪明嘛
Brilliant option.
你是说他可以带我们出去?
You mean it can get us out of here?
我们得登上那艘潜艇
We have to get on that sub.
有很多幸存者
There are more, with survivors.
有一个美国人离开了新斯科舍
One from the U.S., leaving Nova Scotia.
一艘英国潜艇等在英吉利海峡
A British submarine waiting in the English Channel.
天黑得时候我们必须走
We have to go when it's dark.
给我们5到6小时  够了吗?
Gives us five or six hours. Is that enough time?
它说他们在河尽头的北边
It says they are in the north end of the river.
河的更深处
It's deeper there.
你觉得我们可以穿过城市?
You think we can cross the city?
是的
Yeah.
你能帮我一起收下东西吗?
Can you help me gather supplies?
没问题  娃娃
Sure, kid.
我不是娃娃
I am not a kid.
好吧
Got it.
走
Come.
走吧
Let's go.
没事的
We're fine.
-你干过几百次了吧? -是的
-You've done this a hundred times, right? -Yeah.
关上笼子
Just close the cage.
确定锁好了
Make sure it's locked.
赶快
Hurry!
这是什么?
What is this?
自制的
It's homemade.
微波投影仪
It's a microwave projector.
能量从这里出来
Power comes from here,
从那发射微波
and fires incredible microwave there.
它能发射微波
It shoots microwaves.
发射高能微波光线
A focused and compressed microwave beam.
我算过的
I calculate.
密度足够高的微波  能够打破他们的能量场
Enough high-density microwave could break up their energy field.
然后呢?
And what will it do?
打得他们落花流水
Knock them on their ass!
就像  KO他们?
Like, kill them?
慢慢的  先打伤了  然后杀了他们  大概是这样
Slow, wound, kill, perhaps.
想想  他们就像波能
Just think, they're like wave energy,
要是我们能将他们的负荷连起来
and if we can connect their charge,
也就就能创造连锁反应
maybe we create a chain reaction.
一击毙命
Take a bunch out at once.
有用吗?
Does it work?
这就叫以毒攻毒
You fight fire with fire.
对头
Precisely.
喝咖啡
Drink coffee.
世界第一外星人杀手
The world's first alien killer.
这家伙对着猫唱歌
This guy sings to his cat.
看看这只猫  你怎么想?
Yeah. But look at that cat. So what do you think?
我怀疑人类所有的希望  都寄托于科学
I doubt the hope of all humanity lies in sketchy homegrown science.
看  要是有效呢?
Look, what if it works?
-要是炸飞我们呢? -有可能  但要是成功了呢?
-What if it blows us all up? -Yeah, but what if it works?
Vika
Vika.
Vika房间在楼上
Vika, the apartment's upstairs.
不可能成功的  我知道有个藏处我们可以去
You won't make it. I know where we can hide. Come on.
我要去笼子那
I'll take the cage.
不! Annie!
No! Annie!
Annie!
Nat! Nat!
堵住了
It's jammed.
Nat!
Nat  我移不开这张桌子! 移不开!
Nat, I can't move this table! I can't!
吃我一炮
Eat this!
成功了!
We did it!
继续开火
Keep firing!
再揍他!
Hit it again!
Sergei!
快走安全出口  快  快!
Fire escape! Go! Go!
-快点  -不行!
-Come on! -No, don't!
Annie! 快点
Annie! Come on!
不行  我做不到
I can't! I can't!
抓住我的手
Grab my arm!
Annie
Annie.
Sergei先生
Mr. Sergei?
Anne呢?
Where is Anne?
快来
Come on.
继续走
Keep moving.
藏在我们身后
Hide behind us.
这他妈的是啥?
What the hell is this?
我了个...
What the...
跑! 快跑!
Run! Run!
开火!
Fire!
Sasha  快走!
Sasha go!
Boris  准备!
Boris get ready!
开火!
Fire!
好好享用吧  死玩意儿!
You don't like it bitch!
欢迎来到俄罗斯  倒霉蛋
Welcome to Russia, sucker.
谢了
Thank you.
美国人
Americans.
利用外星人侵略家乡
Aliens bad for homeland,
倒是可以赚一笔
but good for business.
那个在放什么?
What's that discharge?
微波
Microwaves.
就像外星人的电击枪那样
Like a big alien stun gun.
这是什么?
What is this?
他们发光的时候也就代表能量用光了
When they generate their lightning, their power drains.
他的隐形盔甲就变弱了
Its invisible shield is weakened.
我们就压抓住这种时机打他们
That's when we strike.
Sean别管那么多了  走吧
Sean, just leave it. Let's go.
我们只有些碎片  所以杀不死他们  只能伤了他们
We have dislodged fragments, but we can only wound them.
但是可以打碎他们的盔甲
Yeah, but their armor cracks.
走吧
Let's go.
Anne的事  很遗憾
I'm sorry about Anne.
你们哪儿来的?
Where are you from?
-西雅图  -好地方
-Seattle. -Ah, Nirvana.
是啊
Yeah.
有需要的话  你们可以一直呆在这里
Well, you can stay here as long as you need.
我可以训练你们
I can train you.
谢了  但我们不能停下来
Thanks, but we have to keep moving.
去哪?
Where?
河里有艘潜艇  早上它就要离开了
There's a submarine in the river, it leaves in the morning.
我们要和同样来自美国的人们汇合
It's joining others. One from the U.S.
潜艇?
Submarine?
-是的  -你们相信那个?
-Yeah. -And you believe that?
你叫什么名字孩子?
What's your name, son?
Sean
Sean.
不可能的  Sean
You won't make it, Sean.
为什么? 我们都努力这么久了
Why not? We made it this far.
不可能的
No.
你们只走了差不多学会广场那么远
You made it as far as Academy Plaza.
我们在这
And we made it here.
我们还可以走更远
And we can make it further.
好吧
Okay.
你想去那里?
You want to go there?
但是这些地方  这里  这里  这里都不能走了
But these areas, here, here, here and here, are overrun.
都是敌人的领地  你们不可能穿过去的
Enemy territory. You can't go through.
你们像这样走?
You want to go around, like this?
那得要五个星期
It would take five weeks.
还要是走运的话
If your luck hasn't run out.
留在这里  你会死
You stay here, you eventually die.
这是我们的家
This is our home.
我们打不过敌人  我们还可以回击  甚至逃跑
When the enemy are this strong, we can strike and run,
照顾那些弱小的
watching for weaknesses.
我们回到原点  但我们绝不退缩
We return to camp, but we never retreat.
是啊
So, yes.
明天我们可能会死  但今天
We'll die tomorrow, but today,
只要我们还活着  就要斩杀敌人直到最后
we will kill at least one of the enemy.
抱歉  我无能为力
I'm sorry, we cannot help you.
我知道  你认为我们不可救药了
I know you think we don't have a chance,
但是我们必须放手一搏
but we have to try.
这不是我们的家
This isn't our home.
Sean说的对  我们要放手一搏
Sean's right, we have to try.
你说得对
You know what? You're right.
要不是因为你  我们也不可能在这
We wouldn't be here if it wasn't for you.
要是不能在家看见同胞  那救他们有什么用?
But what the hell is the point in saving people if you don't see them home?
你们的任务就是呆在这里
Your mission is to dig in here
然后就可以死得不那么痛苦
so you can die in a slightly different way?
而我们的任务是
Here's our mission.
我们得上那艘潜艇
We're going to get on that submarine,
和其他幸存者汇合
get together with whatever other survivors might be out there,
然后一起打回去
and fight the hell back.
为什么不上去呢?
So why don't we get on that sub
再带上些武器
and get you and your men some real weapons?
而不只是留下来打得不痛不痒
Instead of settling for this.
我和你一起
I'm coming with you.
他们还是孩子
They are kids...
我们乘地铁
We'll use the metro.
这是最好的机会
It's our best shot.
我们回来之前  你做指挥
You have command until we get back.
真不错
That's nice work back there.
都是Natalie的功劳
That was all Natalie.
你们听到没?
Are you guys hearing that?
Sasha
Sasha.
前进
Onwards.
你确定?
Are you sure?
快点! 到轨道下面
Come on! Down to the tracks!
我的...
Oh, my...
小心前进!
Stay low!
-Ben! -Vika!
那是什么?
What is that?
天啊
Oh, my God.
Ben  你在做什么?
Ben, what are you doing?
当心
Be careful.
Vika  快来
Vika, come on.
天呐  Ben!
Oh, my God. Ben!
-不! -操!
-No! -Shit!
不
No!
-Sean! -Ben!
不!
No!
Sean
Sean.
我们得赶紧走
We have to go.
快点
Come on.
怎么走? 走哪边?
Which way? Which way?
上船
On that boat.
河朝北边流
The river flows north.
我们可以飘到潜艇那
We will drift to the submarine.
慢点
Get below.
喂
Hey.
没事的
It's okay.
没关系的  这不是你的错
It's okay. It's not your fault.
那时我们的妈妈
Our moms
在家庭教师协会上遇到
were on PTA together.
他在尖子班
He was in the smart class.
他妈妈让他跟我玩
His mom made him play with me.
我永远都忘不了
I sort of never got over it.
我该跟你告别了
I'm thinking we should say goodbye.
什么?
What?
因为我永远也没机会跟Ben这样说
I never got a chance to say it to Ben.
好吧  那...
Okay. Well,
回头见
I'll be seeing you around.
好的
Yeah.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
怎么了?
What's happening?
我们搁浅了
We've run aground.
不是吧
Oh, my God.
所以他们来了  我们挡着路了
This is why they came. We're just in the way.
他们想怎样?
What do they want?
矿产资源丰富
We are mineral-rich.
铜  镍
Copper, nickel.
这些金属都导电
Metals that conduct electricity.
他们肯定是吃这个
It must be food.
在那! 就是那个
There it is!
潜艇!
The submarine.
我们快成功了
We're going to make it.
我们快成功了  我们可以离开这了
We're going to make it. It's our way out.
这是什么?
What is it?
该死
Shit.
Sean!
Natalie!
Natalie?
Sean! 快游!
Sean, swim!
Natalie!
快游啊! 快点!
Swim, now! Swim!
快 把手给我
Here, give me your hand.
赶紧  孩子
Come on, son. Come on.
还有其他人
There's someone else out there.
她叫Natalie  她肯定游到了上游岸上
Her name's Natalie. She must have swam ashore upriver.
我看着你们的船走的
I watched your boat go over.
我不想你们少掉谁  但我们不能在久留了
I don't want to lose this one. We can't wait any longer.
我不会扔下她的
I won't leave her.
有命令说  我不能与幸存者分开
I had orders not to depart without survivors.
-我们现在必须起航  -谁的命令
-Now we have to sail. -Whose orders?
Nikolai lranov长官的命令
Captain Nikolai lvanov.
-我去和他说  他在哪? -已经死了
-I'll speak to him. Where is he? -Dead.
火光!
Flares!
那是她! 是Natalie
That's her. That's Natalie.
我不会叫你离开这的  好吗?
Look, I'm not asking you to go out there, okay?
只是再等等
Just to delay your departure.
这个地方太危险了
This area is infested!
抱歉  但是她能活下来的几率  实在太小了
I'm sorry, but her chances for survival are not good.
她知道该怎么保护自己  相信我
Look, she knows how to hide. Trust me.
要是回到那  你...
You go back out there, your chances...
他知道他该怎么做
He knows what his chances are.
我们失去了很多伙伴
We've all lost comrades.
她还活着
She's alive.
好吧  一个都不能少
And right now, every one of us count.
我们不能扔下她不管
We can't leave her.
要是她是你的伙伴  你也一定会这么想的
If she was one of yours, you'd want the same.
好吧
Okay.
那我们藏到下面  准备个战斗计划
Okay. Let's get under and make a battle plan.
新枪准备好了
The new gun is almost ready.
微波枪给我们增加了胜算
The extra microwave gun gives us a chance.
制造它的人...
The man who built it
尽管可以破坏他们的隐形盔甲
thought we could microwave their invisible shield.
但是要打死他们
But to "F" them up,
Sergei先生说  还需要更多能量
Mr. Sergei said that we need much more power.
足够多的电池  就可以发射出强光
More batteries will launch a stronger beam.
可以开4到5枪
You will get four or five good shots at it.
我们要包好能量包  这样才不会短路
We need to wrap the power packs so they don't short out.
把铅毯子拿出来
Get the lead blankets out of radiation...
快!
Hurry!
等微波枪破坏了他们的防御场
The microwave guns disrupt their defense shields.
我们就可以  用不可思议的俄罗斯子弹
And then we kill it.
杀光它们
With good ol' Russian bullets.
我们到有火光的地方开火  也就是这儿
We get to where the flares were fired, here,
找到姑娘后就出来
find the girl and get out.
我代替Sasha的位置
I'll take Sasha's place!
Boris和我  Yuri和Sean
Boris and me. Yuri and Sean.
拿微波枪的带头
Microwave guns lead.
火光从那个方向过来
Her flares came from that direction.
范围不会很大
There is not much cover.
Natalie!
不管用啊
It's not working.
快走
Let's go.
6点方向! 开火!
Six o'clock! Spread out!
快点
Come on!
打他!
Shoot it!
给点力啊!
Come on.
杀了它!
Kill it!
电击枪有用!
The stun gun, it works!
太棒了
Yeah!
Sean
Sean.
Sean!
Natalie
Natalie.
8点钟方向
Eight o'clock.
这儿有太多了
There's too many.
枪快挺不住了
Our guns won't last.
跟我来
Follow me.
是水
It's water.
水可以导电  可以产生连锁反应
It will connect its charge and create a chain reaction.
你确定?
You are certain?
等他们过来就用微波枪
Wait until they're over the water to fire the microwave gun.
注意两边!
Take the flanks!
我去找Natalie
I'll get Natalie.
准备战斗!
Prepare to fight!
他们停下来了
They stopped before the water.
计划不奏效
The plan is not working.
-Natalie? -Sean!
19路车!
Bus 19!
当心  他们在那儿
Be careful. They're out there.
是Vika! Vika 你在做什么?
It's Vika! Vika, what are you doing?
他从哪儿过来的?
Where did she come from?
起作用了  他们在水的那边
It's working. They're over the water.
我们可以战胜他们!
We can beat them!
Natalie!
Sean!
你回来找我了
You came back for me.
我不会丢下你的
Of course I did.
Sean!
去掌握方向
Get the wheel!
停不下来!
I can't stop it!
坚持住!
Hold on!
-再打再打! -没用啊!
-Shoot it again! -It's not working!
Sean!
电池没电了
The battery is dead!
Sean!
快点  赶紧走
Come on. Let's go.
我们成功了  快走  我们镇住他们了
We did it. Let's go. We got them for now.
快离开这
Let's get out of here.
快点
Come on.
你们真的不一起来?
Are you sure you're not coming?
我们找到核潜艇了
Hell, we got a nuclear submarine.
今天我们学会了战斗
Today, we learned how to fight.
以后可以去教别人拉!
Go, and teach the others what we know.
这是灭掉他们的的最后一天
This is the last day of the extermination,
也是战争开始的第一天
and the first day of war.
你还是这么认为?
No changing your mind?
我们不能再走了
I can go no further.
莫斯科就在我的身后
I have Moscow at my back.
-给你  -那找到了?
-There you are. -Did you get it?
恩  我把坏掉的部分换了
Yes, I replaced the damaged parts.
潜艇里还可以用
It will work inside the sub.
这里是伦敦  我收到了其他地区的信号
Here in London, I picked up signals from others around the globe.
欧洲  亚洲还有美国
Europe, Asia, the States.
人们正在反击
There are people fighting back.
我还联系到了在巴黎的军队
I even had contact with a militia group out of Paris.
他们拿下了矿塔
They took down one of those mining towers.
他们破坏了塔
They destroyed a tower.
我已经听说了各种故事
I've been hearing all types of stories.
都录下来了
I've got them here on tape.
多伦多  利马  秘鲁  柏林和上海
Toronto, Lima, Peru, Berlin and Shanghai...
这只是开始
This is how it starts.
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?
?We will rise against?
?Even though we don't know where we should begin?
?Even though we can't see around the bend?
?Oh, we know, we know that we will rise again?